<?xml version="1.0"?>
<random>
    <comment>Steven is a wiener :eggplant:</comment> 
	<comment>I was standing in the park wondering why frisbees got bigger as they get closer. Then it hit me.</comment> 
	<comment>I dream of a better tomorrow... where chickens can cross roads and not have their motives questioned</comment>
	<comment>When I die, I want to die like my grandmother, who died peacefully in her sleep. Not screaming like all the passengers in her car.</comment>
	<comment>I&amp;apos;m never wrong. I once thought I was wrong, turns out, I was mistaken.</comment>
	<comment>The statistics on sanity are that one out of every four Canadians is suffering from some form of mental illness. Think of your three best friends. If they are okay, then it&amp;apos;s you.</comment>
	<comment>No one will win the battle of the sexes, there is too much flirting with the enemy</comment>
	<comment>I am free of all prejudices. I hate everyone equally.</comment>
	<comment>Last night I was looking at the stars and I wondered... where the hell&amp;apos;s my ceiling!</comment>
	<comment>I&amp;apos;m trying to see things from your point of view, but I can&amp;apos;t get my head that far up your a**.</comment>
	<comment>Whoever said nothing was impossible never tried slamming a revolving door.</comment>
	<comment>Some cause happiness wherever they go. Others whenever they go.</comment>
	<comment>Never play leap frog with a unicorn</comment>
	<comment>When life gives you lemons, make orange juice and leave the world wondering how the hell you did it.</comment>
	<comment>Can I lend a machete to your intellectual thicket? </comment>
	<comment>It&amp;apos;s just a job. Grass grows, birds fly, waves pound the sand. I beat people up.</comment>
	<comment>A man&amp;apos;s got to believe in something. I believe I&amp;apos;ll have another drink.</comment>
	<comment>I am so blue I&amp;apos;m greener than purple.</comment>
	<comment>I stepped on a Corn Flake, now I&amp;apos;m a Cereal Killer</comment>
	<comment>Banana error.</comment>
	<comment>Everyday a grape licks a friendly cow</comment>
	<comment>On a scale from one to ten what is your favourite colour of the alphabet.</comment>
	<comment>The sparkly lamp ate a pillow then punched Larry.</comment>
	<comment>Look, a distraction!</comment>
	<comment>What do you think about the magical yellow unicorn who dances on the rainbow with a spoonful of blue cheese dressing?</comment>
	<comment>If your canoe is stuck in a tree with the headlights on, how many pancakes does it take to get to the moon?</comment>
	<comment>Oh no, you&amp;apos;re one of THEM!!!!</comment>
	<comment>A Zebra licked a DVD</comment>
	<comment>A hotdog on a bridge</comment>
	<comment>For Sale: Parachute. Only used once, never opened, small stain.</comment>
	<comment>For the brave souls who get this far: You are the chosen ones, the valiant knights of programming who toil away, without rest, fixing our most awful code. To you, true saviors, kings of men, I say this: never gonna give you up, never gonna let you down, never gonna run around and desert you. Never gonna make you cry, never gonna say goodbye. Never gonna tell a lie and hurt you.</comment>
	<comment>Dear maintainer: Once you are done trying to &amp;apos;optimize&amp;apos; this routine, and have realized what a terrible mistake that was, please increment the following counter as a warning to the next guy: total_hours_wasted_here = 42</comment>
	<comment>When I wrote this, only God and I understood what I was doing. Now, God only knows</comment>
	<comment>I dedicate all this code, all my work, to my wife, Darlene, who will have to support me and our three children and the dog once it gets released into the public.</comment>
	<comment>#define TRUE FALSE #Happy debugging suckers</comment>
	<comment>return 1; # returns 1</comment>
	<comment>This is O(scary), but seems quick enough in practice.</comment>
</random>